<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mon GDC</string>
    <string name="title_activity_prayer">Praises</string>
    <string name="prayer_title">Pray one for each other</string>
    <string name="praying_list_title">Praying subject</string>
    <string name="sharing_title">Authentic sharing</string>
    <string name="bible_reading_title">Reading</string>
    <string name="bible_reading_current">This week</string>
    <string name="share_title">Sharing</string>
    <string name="pray_title">Praying</string>
    <string name="read_title">Reading</string>
    <string name="man_who_prays">A man who prays</string>
    <string name="women_chatting">Womens chatting</string>
    <string name="custom_questions">My questions</string>
    <string name="sharing_questions">Question Examples</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_1">- How God appeard to you this week ?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_2">- What is he teaching you ?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_3">- How do you answer the call ?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_4">- What will you change ?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_5">- Is there an obstacle in your spiritual progression ?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_6">- Do you want to talk about it ?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_7">- Do you want us to pray for that ?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_8">- Who do you want to pray for?</string>
    <string name="sharing_question_9">- What have you thought about the reading of the week ?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_history">Add a reading</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="notes_hint">Notes</string>
    <string name="notes_text">Write your notes here</string>
    <string name="end_date_text">Reading end date</string>
    <string name="wood_pantin_reading">Wood pantin reading</string>
    <string name="historique">History</string>
    <string name="ajouter"><b><u>Add</u></b></string>
    <string name="ajouter_livre"><b><u>Add book</u></b></string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="pour_commencer">Where to begin?</string>
    <string name="qu_est_ce_qu_un_gdc">What is a GDC?</string>
    <string name="une_rencontre_par_semaine"><b>One meeting a week</b></string>
    <string name="lecture_approfondie_de_la_bible"><b>Deep Bible reading</b></string>
    <string name="annuler">Cancel</string>
    <string name="vecu">" Its purpose: <b> an authentic experience of contagious disciples! </b>"</string>
    <string name="gdc_c_quoi">" It is a small group of no more than three people, in which there is intense communion between these people and God."</string>
    <string name="prier_pour_partenaire_title">" Pray for God to inspire me to be a spiritual partner."</string>
    <string name="reponse_trouver_partenaire">" Example: Lord, with whom could I grow in my faith? Who do I feel <b> confident </b> with to be genuine and eager to go further with you? Thank you because you show me the voice, you inspire me <b> in the time that is yours. </b>"</string>
    <string name="plus_button">Plus button</string>
    <string name="prayer_text">" \"Pray for each other\". It is very encouraging to hear someone pray for you. But the GDC is also <b> open to others </b>. Each meeting ends with a moment of prayer for three people around me who need the presence of God. Thus, prayer changes my view of them, makes me more available, and <b> makes me a witness of Jesus for them. </b>"</string>
    <string name="bible_reading_text">"We have a habit of studying the Bible, reading commentaries or related books and that is important. But it's also good to learn <b> reading the Bible in simple reading </b>, letting the Spirit do the rest. This requires a steady and regular reading. Everyone has to adapt their rhythm. Some read up to 30 chapters a week! The important thing is to find out what rhythm allows me to <b> be rooted in my relationship with God </b>. "</string>
    <string name="sharing_text">" The questions revolve around three axes: <b> my relationship to God, to others, and to myself </b>. They are not there to condemn or judge, but to position oneself, to evoke struggles or sufferings, to become aware of victories and the road traveled, to see the action of God in his life, to imagine this action in the lives of others. These questions are a great way to learn <b> \"letting go\" </b>."</string>
    <string name="open_bible">An opened bible</string>
    <string name="gdc_long">The Growing Group</string>
    <string name="book">Livre</string>
    <string name="begin">Begin</string>
    <string name="end">End</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="history">Historique</string>
    <string name="introduction_text">The application allows you to follow the progress of a GDC and to note certain information.</string>
    <string name="introduction_title">What\'s the point ?</string>
    <string name="hepl_pray_text">" The \"Praying\" section allows you to add prayer topics that you share with your partner."</string>
    <string name="help_share_text">The \"Share\" section explains the course of a meeting and helps to guide the conversation with suggestions for questions to exchange. By pressing \"Add\", you can customize this guide by the questions you want.</string>
    <string name="help_read_text">" The section \"Read\" allows you to note week by week the passages you have read by pressing \"Add\". By pressing \"read\" in front of the reading of the week, you will switch to the beginning of the corresponding text in the Bible YouVersion application."</string>
    <string name="subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
</resources>